premiercarebathing.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy | Premier Care in Bathing®

This privacy policy describes Premier Care in Bathing's current policies and practices with regard to personal data collected by Premier Care through this web site. This privacy policy does not apply to information collected offline or in any other way. The term "personal data" refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, e-mail address or mailing address, and any other information that identifies you personally.

Your Consent

By using this web site or any Premier Bathrooms Web site, you consent to our use of your personal data as described in this privacy policy. 

Notification Of Changes To This Policy

Premier Care in Bathing is continually improving and adding new functionality and features to this web site, and improving and adding to its existing services and programs. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law and the changing nature of technology, Premier Care's data practices will change from time to time. If and when our data practices change, Premier Care will post the changes on this web site to notify you of the changes. We encourage you to check this page frequently.

Personal Data Collected Through This Web Site

The only personal data Premier Care currently collects through this web site is the information you give us when you use our site. This includes, for example, the information you provide when you send us your comments or requests for information. 

Premier Care uses the information you provide for the purposes for which it was originally collected, for example, to respond to your e-mail or provide the services you requested. Premier Care also uses this information to help us improve the content and functionality of our web sites, to better understand the needs and interests of the people and organizations that use our web site, and to improve our products and services. Premier Care may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about organizations, products, services, and other things we believe will be of interest to you or to ask for your support. 

Premier Care may share the personal information you provide to us with consultants and other third parties who act for or on behalf of Premier Care, for further processing or analysis. Premier Care may also share or transfer the personal information you provide to us with third party marketers, who may send you offers for goods and services which you may find of interest. In addition, there may be some other, limited circumstances in which Premier Care may share or transfer the personal information in its databases, for example, to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this web site, to take precautions against legal liability.

Anonymous Data Collected Through Premier Care in Bathing Websites

In addition to the information you provide when you use our web site, Premier Care uses technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our web site. For example, we use technology to track how many visitors access our web site, the date and time of their visit, the length of their stay, and which pages they view. We also use technology to determine which web browsers our visitors use and the address from which they accessed our site.

This technology does not identify you personally. It simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our site. Premier Care uses this anonymous data and shares it with third-parties for various reasons, for example, to improve the content and functionality of our web site, to better understand the needs and interests of our visitors, and to improve our service. 

Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, Premier Care may use temporary "cookies" that collect the first level domain name of the user (for example, if your e-mail address is "name@xyz.com," the cookie collects the "xyz.com" portion of your e-mail address) and the date and time you accessed this Web site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not. At the present time, Premier Care only uses temporary or "session" cookies. These "session" cookies expire when your browser window is closed.

In order for certain applications on the Premier Care websites to function properly, if at all, it is necessary for your computer to accept cookies.

Links to Other Sites

This privacy policy applies only to this web site. This site contains many hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by Premier Care. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators. Premier Care does not control these web sites and is not responsible for their data practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal data about yourself.

Questions About Our Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or concerns about the way Premier Care uses personal data, please contact us via the "Contact Us" link on the home page. If you would like to unsubscribe from the database and the uses described in this policy, please visit www.premiercarebathing.com/email-opt-out/ or write to us at 34750 Van Dyke Ave, Sterling Heights MI 48312.
